Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 11 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1113
    - Local 1113 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1953, undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Conklin to Emspak Regarding Finances, Staff Members, and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, January 15, 1938; 20.
      - Conklin to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 17, 1938; 21.
      - Conklin to Emspak Regarding Finances, Negotiations, and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, February 21, 1938; 22.
      - Conklin to James Matles Regarding Negotiations and Factionalism, July 29, 1938; 23.
      - Conklin to Matles Regarding Lockouts, Unemployment, and Staff Members, November 29, 1938; 24.
      - Conklin to Matles Regarding District 11 and Strikes, December 27, 1938; 25.
      - Conklin to Emspak Regarding Finances and Factionalism, January 22, 1940; 26.
      - Frank Davis to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 11, 1942; 27.
      - Walter Forcey to Emspak Regarding Packinghouse Strikes and Unemployment, March 14, 1949; 28.
      - Evelyn Hanson to UE Regarding Staff Members, September 28, 1951; 29.
      - Hanson to UE Regarding Strikes and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 1952; 30.
      - Hanson to Emspak Regarding Eye-Opener, February 3, 1953; 31.
      - Hanson to Emspak Regarding Strikes, February 17, 1953; 32.
      - Hanson to UE Regarding Strikes and NLRB, March 16, 1953; 33.
      - Hanson to Emspak Regarding Strikes, April 1, 1953; 34.
      - Hanson to Emspak Regarding Strikes, April 6, 1953; 35.
      - Virginia Hoffman to General Executive Board Regarding Factionalism and Local 1121, July 31, 1942; 36.
      - Irene Krueger to Emspak Regarding Withdrawal and Dues, January 23, 1944; 37.
      - Krueger to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 25, 1944; 38.
      - Emil Muelver to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Tenth Anniversary Dance, March 17, 1947; 39.
      - Muelver to Matles Regarding Runaway Shops, January 10, 1948; 40.
      - Muelver to UE Regarding Finances, February 18, 1948; 41.
      - Muelver to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Finances, December 16, 1948; 42.
      - Muelver to Matles Regarding Grievances, Unemployment, and Seniority, February 1, 1952; 43.
      - Muelver to Matles Regarding Finances, May 22, 1952; 44.
      - Muelver to Emspak Regarding Strikes, May 23, 1952; 45.
      - Muelver to Matles Regarding Strikes, January 31, 1953; 46.
      - Muelver to Matles Regarding Strikes, April 3, 1953; 47.
      - Muelver to Emspak Regarding Strikes, April 13, 1953; 48.
      - Muelver to Matles Regarding Strikes and NLRB, July 10, 1953; 49.
      - Muelver to Emspak Regarding Strikes and NLRB, September 9, 1953; 50.
      - Muelver to Fitzgerald Regarding Strikes and Finances, September 29, 1953; 51.
      - Muelver to Matles Regarding Finances, September 29, 1953; 52.
      - Arthur Otto to Emspak Regarding Organization and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, May 10, 1937; 53.
      - Otto to Matles Regarding Factionalism, District 11, Local 1121, and Negotiations, July 31, 1942; 54.
      - Otto to Emspak Regarding Officers and 1942 UE Convention, August 28, 1942; 55.
      - Otto to Emspak Regarding Overtime, October 16, 1942; 56.
      - Otto to Emspak Regarding Overtime, October 24, 1942; 57.
      - Otto to Matles Regarding Contracts and Overtime, November 17, 1942; 58.
      - Otto to Emspak Regarding Overtime and Grievances, November 17, 1942; 59.
      - Otto to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Grievances, March 6, 1943; 60.
      - Otto to Fitzgerald Regarding Conscription, n.d.; 61.
      - Ellen Ruether to Emspak Regarding Seniority, July 19, 1937; 62.
      - Ruether to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 9, 1937; 63.
      - Walter Schmirler to Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations, November 19, 1945; 64.
      - Helen Schultz to Emspak Regarding Contracts and Firings, July 9, 1941; 65.
      - Schultz to Emspak Regarding Constitution, January 1942; 66.
      - Alice Seehafer to UE Regarding Dues, September 11, 1947; 67.
      - Delbert Stanton to Emspak Regarding Runaway Shops, May 28, 1940; 68.
      - Leo Thomas to Emspak Regarding Political Action, October 13, 1944; 69.
      - Robert Weiland to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 15, 1943; 70.
    - Local 1113 Per Capita Reports, June 1937-July 1938 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Local 1113 Financial Information, 1937, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 74)
      - Report of Financial Secretary, July 1937; 1.
      - Lockout Balance Sheet, June 6, 1953; 2.
    - Local 1113 Newspapers, Closed Gates, July 24-25, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Local 1113 Leaflets, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - "Dear Brothers" Regarding Strikes with April 22, 1952, Ernest DeMaio Letter to All Local Unions, April 21, 1952; 1.
      - "These People Crossed Our Picket Line", May 19, 1952; 2.
    - Local 1113 Newspaper Clippings, 1940-1952 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - "Eye Factory for Dubuove" with April 9, 1940, James Matles Letter to Byron Buck, 1.
      - "Strike Vote Looms", 1946; 2.
      - "Dispute Closes Marathon Electric", February 29, 1952; 3.
      - "At 2PM" Regarding Strike, February 29, 1952; 4.
      - "Marathon Electric" Regarding Strike, March 1, 1952; 5.
      - "Marathon Electric Remains Idle", March 1, 1952; 6.
      - "The Employees" Regarding Strike, March 3, 1952; 7.
      - "Help Wanted" Regarding Strike, March 3, 1952; 8.
      - "Local Firm is Picketed", March 4, 1952; 9.
      - "Help Wanted" Regarding Strike, March 4, 1952; 10.
      - "An Answer to an Advertisement" Regarding Strike and Congress of Industrial Organizations, March 5, 1952; 11.
      - "Marathon Electric Lockout Continues", March 5, 1952; 12.
      - "The Lock-out Continues", March 5, 1952; 13.
      - "Marathon Electric" Regarding Strikes, March 5, 1952; 14-15.
      - "Marathon Electric Lockout Continues", March 7, 1952; 16.
      - "We Are Quoting" Regarding Strikes, March 7, 1952; 17.
      - "Help Wanted" Regarding Strikes, March 8, 1952; 18-19.
      - "600 Pickets Gather", March 10, 1952; 20.
      - "Help Wanted" Regarding Strike, March 11, 1952; 21.
      - "Retraction" Regarding Strikes, March 11, 1952; 22.
      - "We Are Delegates" Regarding Strikes, March 11, 1952; 23.
      - "The Wausau Central Labor Union AFL" Regarding Strikes, March 13, 1952; 24.
      - "Marathon Electric Workers" Regarding Strike, March 13, 1952; 25.
      - "Help Wanted" Regarding Strike, March 13, 1952; 26.
    - Local 1113 Bonding Claim, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Albert Olson to Stella Abrams, January 12, 1940; 1.
      - Olson to Julius Emspak, February 23, 1940; 2.
    - Local 1113 Buck Firing, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Byron Buck to Jack Allar, December 3, 1941; 1.
      - Buck to Julius Emspak, December 3, 1941; 2.
      - Buck to Emspak, December 9, 1941; 3.
    - Local 1113 Finances and Factionalism, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Laurence Jacobsen to Julius Emspak, December 17, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Jacobsen with Per Capita List, December 22, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Jacobsen, February 17, 1943; 3.
      - James Matles to Jacobsen, May 4, 1943; 4.
    - Local 1113 Lockout, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Philip Smith to James Matles, July 11, 1946; 1.
      - Smith to Matles, 1946; 2.
      - Local 111B Statement, 1946; 3.
    - Local 1113 Lockout, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - Ernest DeMaio to All UE Locals, March 20, 1952; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to DeMaio, April 9, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, April 18, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, April 25, 1952; 4.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, May 13, 1952; 5.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, May 21, 1952; 6.
      - James Matles to Michael Essin, June 3, 1952; 7.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, June 4, 1952; 8.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, June 12, 1952; 9.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, June 25, 1952; 10.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, July 1, 1952; 11.
      - DeMaio to David Ratner, July 24, 1952; 12.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, July 28, 1952; 13.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, July 30, 1952; 14.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, August 6, 1952; 15.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, August 12, 1952; 16.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, August 20, 1952; 17.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, August 26, 1952; 18.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, September 2, 1952; 19.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, September 11, 1952; 20.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, September 22, 1952; 21.
      - DeMaio to Matles, September 23, 1952; 22.
      - Matles to DeMaio, September 24, 1952; 23.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, September 29, 1952; 24.
      - Matles Memo to Albert Fitzgerald, February 11, 1953; 25.
      - Note, October 1953; 26.
      - Excerpt of Muelver Report, November 1953; 27.
    - Local 1113 Miscellaneous, 1938-1955 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Bishop to James Carey Regarding Strikes, November 19, 1938; 1.
      - Wage Scale, January 1939; 2.
      - Radio Broadcast, March 26, 1939; 3.
      - Carey to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 6, 1939; 4.
      - Memo, February 1940; 5.
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Per Capita, July 12, 1943; 6.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, January 10, 1946; 7.
      - Phil Smity to DemMaio Regarding Factionalism and Unemployment, January 8, 1949; 8.
      - Smity to Matles Regarding Taft Hartley Affidavits, December 12, 1949; 9.
      - Emspak to Hecla Press Regarding Finances and National Labor Relations Board, February 17, 1955; 10.
  - Local 1114
    - Local 1114 Constitution, 1947-1954 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Constitution with February 6, 1947, Louis Torre Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, January 1947; 1.
      - Constitution with December 29, 1948, Torre Letter to Fitzgerald, December 1948; 2.
      - Constitution, March 1954; 3.
    - Local 1114 Officers Lists, October 14, 1939-August 10, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Local 1114 Officer Minutes with Report, October 21, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Local 1114 Officers Resolutions, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - Officer Resolution Regarding Harry Bridges' Case with February 12, 1945, Louis Torre Letter to UE, February 8, 1945; 1.
      - Officer Resolution Regarding Factionalism and Illinois Congress of Industrial Organizations with September 4, 1947, Torre Letter to Philip Murray, September 1947; 2.
    - Local 1114 Membership Resolutions, 1940-1943 (Box 6, Folder 88)
      - Membership Resolution Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, June 28, 1940; 1.
      - Membership Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, 1943; 2.
    - Local 1114 Louis Torre Incoming Correspondence, 1941-1949 (Box 6, Folder 89)
      - Janet Barish to Louis Torre Regarding Finances, December 7, 1943; 1.
      - John Daly to Torre Regarding War Labor Board and Fotte Gear Negotiations, September 14, 1945; 2.
      - Peg Darin to Torre Regarding Finances, August 21, 1942; 3.
      - Ernest DeMaio to Torre Regarding Ahlberg Bearing Negotiations, August 6, 1946; 4.
      - Julius Emspak to Torre Regarding Finances, December 1, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Finances, January 9, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Finances, February 2, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Finances, March 26, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Political Action, September 25, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Finances, April 16, 1943; 10.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Westinghouse Negotiations, August 30, 1943; 11.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Illinois Gear Organization, September 29, 1943; 12.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dues, November 11, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Tool and Die Organization, December 14, 1943; 14.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Conscription, December 16, 1953; 15.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Per Capita, January 4, 1944; 16.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding White Collar Workers Organization, April 20, 1944; 17.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dues and D.O. James Manufacturing, July 27, 1944; 18.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Local Picnic and Insurance, August 11, 1944; 19.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Chicago Visit, October 4, 1944; 20.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dues and Veterans, October 16, 1944; 21.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Staff Finances, December 29, 1944; 22.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Factionalism, Local 1150, and Organization at Goodman Manufacturing and Clayton Mark, January 23, 1945; 23.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dues, John Wood Manufacturing Organization, and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, January 23, 1945; 24.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Foremen Organization, March 13, 1945; 25.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dauly Machine Organization and Dues, June 1, 1945; 26.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dauly Machine Organization and Dues, June 11, 1945; 27.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Mercury Manufacturing Negotiations, October 8, 1945; 28.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dues, Cribben and Sexton, and Hubbard Spool, October 30, 1945; 29.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Ampro Organization and Dues, November 12, 1945; 30.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dues, November 30, 1945; 31.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Dues and Dauly Machine, April 22, 1946; 32.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Finances, July 31, 1946; 33.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Foreign Policy and Political Action, April 8, 1947; 34.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Finances, May 27, 1947; 35.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding Mercury Manufacturing Strikes, June 11, 1947; 36.
      - Emspak to Torre Regarding John Wood Strikes, August 23, 1948; 37.
      - Norma Gould to Torre Regarding Foote Gear Organization, July 1, 1942; 38.
      - James Matles to Torre Regarding Strikes, September 15, 1941; 39.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Unemployment, November 25, 1941; 40.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Finances, December 22, 1941; 41.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Overtime, January 22, 1942; 42.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Foote Gear Organization, July 6, 1942; 43.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members, September 22, 1942; 44.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Dauly Machine and Negotiations, September 26, 1942; 45.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members, November 19, 1942; 46.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, March 4, 1943; 47.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Negotiations, November 13, 1945; 48.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Negotiations, November 15, 1945; 49.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members, November 26, 1945; 50.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Strikes and Foote Gear Contract, December 17, 1945; 51.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Combustion Engineering, United Steelworkers of America, and Boilermakers, June 29, 1946; 52.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Organization and Factionalism, July 18, 1946; 53.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members, October 4, 1946; 54.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Mailing List, December 4, 1946; 55.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Western Electric Organization, February 18, 1947; 56.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Factionalism, July 23, 1947; 57.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, October 27, 1947; 58.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding New York City Meeting, February 19, 1948; 59.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members and Chicago Visit, February 2, 1949; 60.
      - Matles to Torre Regarding Staff Members, February 8, 1949; 61.
      - Don Pinkston to Torre Regarding White Collar Workers Organization, March 15, 1946; 62.
      - David Ratner to Torre Regarding Staff Members, March 6, 1946; 63.
      - Ben Riskin to Torre Regarding Ampro, June 7, 1946; 64.
      - Riskin to Torre Regarding Ampro and General Percision Contracts, June 18, 1946; 65.
      - George Rooney to Torre Regarding Hertner and International Projector Negotiations, December 24, 1947; 66.
      - A.N. Towsen to Torre Regarding Wages, Incentive Pay, and Foote Gear, December 13, 1943; 67.
    - Local 1114 Louis Torre Outgoing Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 90)
      - Louis Torre to James Matles Regarding Eagle Grinding Contract, Foote Gear and Stewart Warner Organization, and Staff Finances, August 11, 1941; 1.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Foote Gear Negotiations with Letter to John Steelman, September 10, 1941; 2.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Foote Gear Strike and Organization, September 1941; 3.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Baumbach Manufacturing Contract, Organization, and Officers with October 29, 1941, Letter to Neal McGillicuddy, October 30, 1941; 4.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Unemployment, November 17, 1941; 5.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Gaumbach Contract and Danly Machine Organization, December 2, 1941; 6.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Hanson Scale, December 3, 1941; 7.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Finances, December 18, 1941; 8.
      - Torre to Julius Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board Negotiations and Foote Gear, January 7, 1942; 9.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Overtime, January 20, 1942; 10.
      - Torre to UE Regarding Decca Wages, January 28, 1942; 11.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Plant Closeures, Negotiations and Organization, March 25, 1942; 12.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding 53rd St. and Chicago Foote Gear Organization and War Labor Board, June 24, 1942; 13.
      - Torre to John Steelman Regarding WLB and Merdle-Korf Organization, August 20, 1942; 14.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Organization, Staff Members, Contracts, Negotiations, and WLB, November 10, 1942; 15.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Tuthill Pump and Grievances, December 3, 1942; 16.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Finances, December 4, 1942; 17.
    - Local 1114 Louis Torre Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 91)
      - Louis Torre to Neil Brant Regarding War Labor Board and Negotiations, December 23, 1942; 1.
      - Torre to James Matles Regarding Contracts and Negotiations, December 31, 1942; 2.
      - Torre to Neil Brant Regarding WLB, January 26, 1943; 3.
      - Torre to Gus Towsen Regarding Insurance, WLB, and Wages, January 26, 1943; 4.
      - Torre to Robert Wise Regarding Productivity, February 4, 1943; 5.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding American Gear Lockout, February 5, 1943; 6.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Staff Members, Organization, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, Women, and Lockouts, February 24, 1943; 7.
      - Torre to Matles Regarding Finances, March 30, 1943; 8.
      - Torre to Julius Emspak Regarding Tourek and Armstrong Blum Negotiations and WLB, May 22, 1943; 9.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Insurance, June 3, 1943; 10.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Incentive and Check-off, August 28, 1943; 11.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Foote Gear Negotiations, September 21, 1943; 12.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Illinois Gear Organization and Finances, September 27, 1943; 13.
      - Torre to Ray Klausner Regarding Officers, October 4, 1943; 14.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off and Foote Gear, November 9, 1943; 15.
      - Torre to Draft Board Regarding Conscription, December 2, 1943; 16.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 4, 1943; 17.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Conscription, December 4, 1943; 18.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Employment and Midwestern Tool, December 9, 1943; 19.
    - Local 1114 Louis Torre Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - Louis Torre to William Davis Regarding Ahlberg Bearing Strike, Firings, and War Labor Board, December 15, 1943; 1.
      - Torre to Julius Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Miehle Press Organization, January 19, 1944; 2.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, January 31, 1944; 3.
      - Torre to United Auto Workers Regarding Ahlberg Bearing and WLB, February 12, 1944; 4.
      - Torre to Gus Towsen Regarding Ahlberg Bearing and WLB, February 12, 1944; 5.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, February 15, 1944; 6.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Foote Gear White Collar Organization and United Office and Professional Workers of America Inter-union Rivalry, April 12, 1944; 7.
      - Torre to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Political Action, April 12, 1944; 8.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Political Action, April 12, 1944; 9.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Political Action, April 21, 1944; 10.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding James Manufacturing Organization and Per Capita, July 13, 1944; 11.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Local Picnic and Staff Finances, July 13, 1944; 12.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Scully Jones Organization, October 14, 1944; 13.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Goodman Manufacturing Organization, Factionalism, and Local 1150, October 24, 1944; 14.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Miehle Press Organization, Unemployment, and Chicago Organization, November 17, 1944; 15.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, December 22, 1944; 16.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers Organization, December 22, 1944; 17.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 22, 1944; 18.
    - Local 1114 Louis Torre Outgoing Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 93)
      - Louis Torre to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 22, 1944; 1.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Goodman Manufacturing, Clayton Mark, Factionalism, and Local 1150, January 6, 1945; 2.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding John Wood and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, January 10, 1946; 3.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding John Wood Manufacturing and AFL Inter-union Rivalry, January 31, 1945; 4.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Foote Gear Foremen and Organization, March 2, 1945; 5.
      - Torre to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Illinois Tool Organization, March 15, 1945; 6.
      - Torre to Walter Harris Regarding Bell & Howell and Onsrod Machine Organization, Congress of Industrial Organizations, and Inter-union Rivalry with UAW and Optical Workers, April 18, 1945; 7.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Danly Machine Membership Drive and Dues, May 24, 1945; 8.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances and Negotiations, May 24, 1945; 9.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Danly Machine Membership Drive and Dues, June 8, 1945; 10.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, August 10, 1945; 11.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Picnic, August 10, 1945; 12.
      - Torre to Lewis Schwellenbach Regarding Foote Gear Negotiations, September 5, 1945; 13.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, Political Action, Wages, and Organization, September 11, 1945; 14.
      - Torre to Secretary of Labor Regarding Illinois Gear Negotiations and War Labor Board, October 2, 1945; 15.
      - Torre to Secretary of Labor Regarding Mercury Manufacturing Negotiations and National Labor Relations Board, October 4, 1945; 16.
      - Torre to Schwellenbach Regarding James Manufacturing Negotiations and WLB, October 17, 1945; 17.
      - Torre to Schwellenbach Regarding Ahlberg Bearing Negotiations and WLB, October 19, 1945; 18.
      - Torre to Emspak Regarding Hubbard Spool and Cribben Sexton Organization, October 23, 1945; 19.
      - Torre to Schwellenbach Regarding Merkle Koff Negotiations and WLB, October 23, 1945; 20.
      - Torre to Schwellenbach Regarding Gear Specialities Negotiations and WLB, October 25, 1945; 21.
    - Local 1114 Louis Torre Outgoing Correspondence, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Louis Torre to John Daly Regarding War Labor Board and Negotiations, November 5, 1945; 1.
      - Torre to Neil Brant Regarding WLB, November 5, 1945; 2.
      - Torre to James Matles Regarding Negotiations, November 5, 1945; 3.